比分是多少
What are we at?
八比九
Eight to nine.
所以
So...
我还赢着呢
still winning.
最多不超过十秒
For about 10 more seconds.
你也要走吗
You, too?
是的
Yeah.
我刚和玛姬谈过
I just talked to Maggie.
她说了什么
What'd she say?
没说多少
Not much.
只是给我了这个
Just gave me this.
去最近联邦哨站的地图
Directions to the nearest Commonwealth checkpoint.
这是士兵留下的  以防有人改主意
Troopers left them in case people changed their minds.
嗯  很多人都改了
Yeah. A lot of people are.
是啊
Yeah...
但你会回来的
You'll be back, though.
对吧
Right?
我想是的
Yeah, I think so.
好吧
Okay.
试试呀
Shoot your shot!
需要人护送你吗
You need an escort?
为什么
Why?
路途遥远  知道吗
It's a long walk, you know?
你可能会无聊  仅此而已
Might get bored. That's all.
有人骑马来了
We got a rider coming!
是谁
Who is it?
不是我们认识的人
Nobody we know.
停在原地
Hold where you are!
停下  不然我们就射了
Hold, or we will shoot!
他中枪了  快叫人
He's been shot! Get help!
恶魔...
Devils...
他们屠杀了他们
They're slaughtering them.
骗子...
Liars...
你们一定要去...
You've got to go...
好...
Yes...
YYsub.net
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视资讯
请访问 www.YYsub.net
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译      送小孩
校对      送小孩
时间轴      西·查   加森
后期      雷鸣  拉图
总监      送小孩
行尸走肉
第十一季  第十三集
我们不去
We're not going.
玛姬  他拼死求助我们
Maggie, he died begging for our help.
我理解
I understand it.
但我们自顾不暇
But we're barely holding on as it is.
一定是我们认识的人派他来的
Someone we know must've sent him.
可能是联邦的人  或者是乔吉...
Could be from the Commonwealth, or Georgie --
或者是个陷阱
Or it could be a trap.
我们去帮忙  山顶寨将任人宰割
We go to help and leave the Hilltop open to attack.
我觉得这不是陷阱
I don't think it's a trick.
他很害怕  他没说谎
He was scared. He wasn't lying.
就算他没说谎
Even if he wasn't,
我们人手不足  不能去和其他团体战斗
we can't go up against another group without the people to fight them.
我们没这个条件
We don't have that.
不是说要接纳所有需要帮助的人吗
What happened to taking in whoever was in need?
寡不敌众从来没有阻止过你
Being outnumbered has never stopped you before.
也许我应该被阻止
Maybe it should have.
我们只是在勉强维持着
We're barely holding on.
听起来那些人也一样
It sounds like these people are, too.
那些人正是我妈妈的目标  而我也帮过她
That's exactly who my mother would've targeted, and I helped.
我不会让这种事再发生在别人身上
I'm not letting it happen to someone else.
所以你不走了
So you're not leaving.
我还是要走  只是...
I am. I'm just...
我必须先帮这些人
I have to help these people first.
半路换你开
You take over at the halfway mark.
妈妈
Mom!
这次要多久
How long this time?
我总是对你说什么
What do I always tell you?
-要多久就多久  -对
- As long as it takes. - That's right.
我走后  你会守住这里吗
You're gonna hold down the fort while I'm gone?
设好防线  保持警惕
Keep a perimeter, stay on alert.
-好  祝你好运  -谢谢
- You got it. Good luck. - Thank you.
帮我拿着
Could you get that for me?
你为什么不接受他们的帮助
Why don't you want their help?
联邦的
The Commonwealth's.
因为没帮助我们也能熬过去
Because we can get by without it.
我们为什么非要"熬"
Why do we have to just "Get by"?
这只是暂时的
It's only temporary.
轻松并不意味着更好
What's easier isn't always better.
在灾变前
You know, before the Fall,
我与家人和父亲住在一个农场里
I lived on a farm with my family and my dad.
有一天  一群企业农场开发者
One day, these corporate farm developers
开始敲我们家的门  想收购我们
started knocking on our door, trying to buy us out.
我父亲一直不同意
My dad kept saying no.
然后有一天  出现了严重的干旱
Then, one day, this bad drought hit.
开发者再次来敲门了
The developers started knocking again,
不过这一次  他们出了农场价值的三倍
except this time, they offered three times what the farm was worth.
他们知道我们负债累累  走投无路
They knew we were in debt and desperate.
但他们也知道  干旱终将结束
But they also knew the drought would end
农场会再次盈利
and the farm would become profitable again,
所以他们只需要耗赢我们
and all they had to do was outlast us.
他们开始留下一箱箱的食物
They start dropping off crates of food
来"帮助"喂养牲畜
to "Help" with the livestock.
而他只是留食物在门廊上腐烂
And he would just let it sit there on the porch and rot
好让他们下次来送时看到
so they'd see it when the next shipment came.
他说我们受到了考验
He said that we were being tested.
猜猜发生了什么
And guess what happened.
干旱结束了
The drought ended.
我们重振旗鼓
We got back on our feet.
那些开发者再也没来找过我们
And those developers never bothered us again.
你父亲为什么让食物腐烂
Why'd your dad let the food rot?
因为如果他们看到我们拿了
If they'd seen us take it,
就会知道我们需要食物
they would've known we needed them
然后永远不会放过我们
and never left us alone.
但牲畜在挨饿啊
But the cattle were hungry.
我们没损失任何牲畜
We didn't lose any.
我们团结一心  挺了过去
We stuck together, and we made it through.
对  你们"熬"了过去
Yeah, you "Got by."
只是
It's just...
我这一辈子都被要求"熬"下去
"Getting by" Is what I've been forced to do my whole life.
我听说这能让你更强大和聪明
I was told that it makes you stronger and wiser.
但事实并非如此
But it doesn't.
这会伤害你
It hurts.
换你会怎么做
What would you have done?
问问大家想怎么做
Asked everyone what they wanted
而不是替他们做决定
instead of deciding for them.
我是在这样做吗
Is that what I'm doing?
你认为联邦懂得更多吗
You think The Commonwealth knows better?
这样想很疯狂吗
Is that crazy to think?
是的
Yes.
那些人十年来没受过任何考验
Those people have not been tested for 10 years.
当考验来临时  你难道想待在那里吗
Do you wanna be there when they are?
我只是
I just...
希望每天过上平稳的生活
want things to be the same every day.
你同意吗
Do you agree?
大部分都同意
With most of it, yeah.
当心
Whoa! Look out!
刀直接刺穿护颈
Knife slashed right through the neck guard.
盔甲缝隙处中枪
Shot between the armor gaps.
玛姬
Maggie!
是亚伦
It's Aaron.
一周前
联邦第一基督教堂
上帝已经准备好了道路
祂只是在等你准备好
这不仅源于仇恨
But not only is it borne of hate,
还源于爱  友谊和恐惧
but from love and from friendship, and from fear.
在《路加福音》第15章12节中
And in Luke 15:12,
耶稣说一个富有父亲的任性儿子
Christ speaks of a rich father's wayward son
自私地前往了远方
that selfishly set off to distant lands,
他任意放荡  将钱财挥霍一空
who squandered his riches on decadence and wild living.
然后  儿子发现他的灵魂是空虚的
And then, the son found his soul empty.
他需要帮助
And he was in need.
他回到了父亲身边  乞求他的原谅
And he went back to his father and begged for forgiveness.
他的父亲拥抱了他
And his father embraced him,
因为他的儿子"死而复生
for his son "Was dead, and is now alive.
失而复得"
He was lost, and now is found."
现在  当我今天要求你们
Now, there were a lot of stunned faces
坐在陌生人旁边时  很多人一脸惊讶
when I asked all of you to sit by a stranger today,
我现在仍能看到很多人对此感到尴尬
and I'm still seeing a lot of awkwardness with the arrangement.
很多人背部僵硬  夹紧了屁股
A lot of stiff backs, clenched butt cheeks.
为什么
Why?
你们中有些人曾在废土生活过
Those of you that were out there in the wasteland,
在那里  你们从认识的人
you know from the people you found,
和依赖的人身上学到了
from the ones you could rely upon,
即使你们之前不相识也没关系
that it didn't matter that you were strangers beforehand, did it?
你们被迫看到了彼此的人性
You were forced to see the humanity in each other,
虽然没有血缘关系
and though not bound by blood,
但这些陌生人成了超越朋友的存在
these strangers became more than friends,
他们成了家人
they became family.
为什么在外面是那样
Why is it that way out there...
在里面却不是呢
but not that way in here?
《罗马书》第3章第23节
Romans 3:23 --
"因为世人都犯了罪  亏缺了神的荣耀"
"For all have sinned and fall short of the glory of God."
我再重复一遍  "世人都犯了罪"
Now let me repeat that -- "All of us have sinned."
这正是将我们联系在一起的纽带
And that is the very thread that binds us together.
如果你剥离自己的表面标签
And if you strip yourselves of the superficial labels --
比如工作  住处  收入
what do we do, where do I live, how much money do I have --
如果你剥离了这些
if you strip yourselves of that,
你就会看到身边人最真实的样子
it will make you see the person by your side
就像你在镜中看到的自己一样
as you see yourself in the mirror.
世界毁灭前我们的生活方式
And the way we were before the world fell
一定不会是我们今后的生活方式
cannot be the way we are moving forward.
我们必须永远牢记这个纽带
We must always remember the thread,
这样我们才能勇敢尝试
for that is what makes us try,
才能原谅  才能复苏
it makes us forgive, it makes us return from peril.
才能成为
It makes us...
我们自己
us.
听起来像你在拍我马屁
Sounds like you're blowing smoke up my ass.
不  你讲得很好
No, you were great.
我还以为你会讲什么烈火炼狱
I -- I was expecting a little more fire and brimstone, I guess.
你看起来很开心
You look happy.
我可能真的很开心
I think I might be.
所以刚才的那个...
So all that up there, that was...
不  那不是演戏
No, it's, uh -- it's not an act.
一开始  我只是装装样子
I mean, in the beginning, I was just going through the motions,
但从某一天开始  我不用装了
but then, one day, I just wasn't.
就好像按下了某个开关
It was like a switch was flipped,
我能再次听到祂的声音了
and I could hear Him again.
嗯
Yeah.
我们经历过的地狱
That hell we went through,
感觉就像不是真的
it almost feels like it wasn't real.
就像只是一场噩梦
Like it was just a nightmare or something.
亚历山大怎么样了
What about Alexandria?
联邦为重建投入了更多人力和资源
Oh, Commonwealth's pouring even more manpower and resources into the rebuild.
但在重建的同时
But, uh, while that's getting finished up,
他们要我为新移民计划帮忙
they've asked me to, uh, help out with their new immigration initiative.
我们刚来时  他们可不喜欢移民
They didn't seem too keen on immigrants when we came in.
以前是不喜欢
They weren't.
在他们听说我曾为非政府组织工作过后
And after they heard that I worked for an NGO back in the day,
他们让我重审了纳新政策
they asked me to review their intake policies.
现在我们正在伸出援手  接纳需要帮助的人
Now we're reaching out and bringing in people that need help.
上帝的工作
The Lord's work.
对
Yeah.
实际上
Actually, that's, um...
我就是为此而来的
That's why I'm here.
有一个四十人左右的团体
There's a group of about 40 people
盘踞在弗吉尼亚州西部边境的一座公寓楼里
holed up in an apartment complex on the western border of Virginia.
我们想接触他们  提供帮助
We want to make first contact and offer them help.
上面的一些人
Some of the folks upstairs, um...
认为带上你是个好主意
they thought it'd be a good idea if you tag along.
为什么是我
Why me?
那是个
It's a...
宗教团体  所以
religious group, so...
那附近有敌人吗
Any hostiles in the territory?
我们会带上部队  以防万一
We'll have troops with us, just in case.
我的上级卡尔森也会跟着我们
Also, my boss, Carlson, will be with us.
他这个人有点...
He's a little, um...
你会看到的  但是
Well, you'll see, but...
他的心是好的
his heart's in the right place.
抱歉打扰
Sorry to interrupt, uh...
卡尔森准备好了  只等你了
Carlson's ready when you are.
谢谢  杰西
Oh. Thank you, Jesse.
新人  我们正在训练他
New kid. We're training him.
你去不去
What do you say?
你对这些人了解多少
What do you know about these people?
据侦察部队说
According to the scouts, they're, uh,
他们只是一群友好的定居者
just a friendly group of settlers.
天啊  你们感觉到了吗
God, do you feel that?
那种冲动
That rush?
多巴胺和肾上腺素混在一起  真是...
That mix of dopamine and adrenaline, just...
就是那种期待感
It's just, that anticipation...
我们将改变生活
We're gonna change lives.
你
You.
And you.
甚至还有你  杰西
And even you, too, Jesse.
今天  我们会让世界
Today, we're gonna make the world
变得比昨天好一点点
just a little bit better than it was yesterday.
你不是说他们是"友好的定居者"吗
I thought you said these were "Friendly settlers."
看起来不太友好啊
That doesn't look friendly.
你觉得不友好吗
You don't think so?
嗯
No.
好吧
Okay.
不友好又怎样
What if they aren't?
就算他们生气
If they're angry,
也只是因为他们害怕
that just means they're afraid.
等他们和你见了面  就没事了
When they meet you, they won't be.
天啊  我等不及看你俩大显神通了
Man, I cannot wait to watch you two do your thing.
他要跟我们一起去吗
Is he going in with us?
他通常都会去
He usually does, yeah.
但他不会说话
But he's not gonna do any of the talking.
而且周围有援军
And we'll have backup nearby.
你确定吗
You sure?
他们在扎营吗
Are they setting up camp?
是的
That they are.
所以他们不跟我们一起去吗
So they're not coming with us?
这个嘛
Well...
最好别吓到当地居民
better not spook the natives.
别担心
But don't worry.
他们离得很近
They're just a chirp away.
克罗中士  能收到吗  完毕
Sergeant Crowe, do you copy? Over.
收到  长官  完毕
Copy, sir. Over.
看到了吧
You see?
没问题的
It's all good!
好吧  我不去了
Yeah, I'm not doing this.
这种地方里面通常都有个老头
Places like that usually have some old man
拿着猎枪   等着某个蠢货
with a shotgun inside just looking for an excuse
踩上门口的草坪  好找借口杀了他
to kill some dumbass who stepped on his front lawn.
这地方就像贴着"请勿打扰"
Practically screams "Do not disturb."
对
Yeah.
我同意
I agree.
一切还好吗
Hey! Is everything alright?
我们对此不太确定
We're not so sure about this.
或许最好别惹他们
Might be better to leave them alone.
放弃任务
Abort?
就因为临阵紧张吗
Just because of some pre-game jitters?
不  因为你的计划是狗屎
No, because your plan is shit,
而我不想死  仅此而已
and I don't want to die. That's all.
我以前做过这种事
I've done it before.
这不过是再做一次
We'll do it again.
你找到过的最大的团体有多少人
What's the largest group you've found?
四个人
Four.
那里面有四十个人吗
And there are 40 in there?
所以呢
So?
所以  那么多人
So, with that many people,
只要有一个人神经紧张
all it takes is one nervous guy
管不住扣扳机的手  事情就会搞砸
with an itchy trigger finger to set things off.
-我觉得你不明白...  -不  等等
- I don't think you appreciate - No, no, no, hold on.
他说得对  我们没应对过这种事  结束了
He's right. Alright, we've never dealt with it, it's game over.
两位
Guys,
没有商量的余地
it's not up for discussion.
我需要你们相信我知道我在做什么
I need you to trust that I know what I'm doing.
走吧
So, let's go.
好吧
Fine.
我需要你戴着那个
Hey, I need you to wear that.
那是你...
It's part of your, um...
戏服的一部分
costume.
这没得商量
This is how this is going to go.
你好
Hello!
我叫亚伦
My name is Aaron!
我们来自一个叫联邦的社区
We come from a community called The Commonwealth.
我们想伸出友谊之手
We'd like to extend our friendship.
我们的人
Our people...
在你们能找到的地方留下了这个
left these where you would find them.
因为全被拿走了  所以我猜你们找到了
Since they're all gone, I'm assuming you did.
美军即食口粮
鸡肉有点难嚼  但是
The chicken's a little rubbery, but...
能充饥就行
it does the job.
我们的营地里还有更多  如果你们想要的话
We have more back at our camp, if you'd like.
我能和谁谈谈吗
Is there anyone I could speak with?
面对面地谈谈
Face-to-face?
武器
Weapons.
这个
Oh. Uh...
不太容易取下来
It's kind of a bitch to take off.
只有你们四人吗
Just the four of you?
附近还有一队维和者
There's a group of peacekeepers nearby,
等着我们报平安
waiting for us to check in.
真吓人
Sounds scary.
小心总没错  对吧
Can't be too safe now, can we?
右边最后一扇门
Last door to the right.
门后有什么
What's down there?
坐
Seats.
我叫亚伦
I'm Aaron.
如我在外面所说
And like I said outside,
我们来自一个叫联邦的社区
we come from a community called the Commonwealth.
那里...
And it's, uh...
有点像过去的世界
Well, it's a bit like the old world.
五万人住在那里
50,000 people live there.
我们有运作正常的政府
We have a functioning government,
防护墙  人人都有房住
protective walls, housing for everyone,
餐厅  两家电影院
restaurants, two movie theaters --
士兵
Soldiers?
和教堂也有吧
And churches, too, I take it.
对吧  神父
Eh, Father?
你的领子是丢了吗
Did you lose your collar?
我想让你在知道我的职务前
Wanted you to see who I was
先了解我这个人
before learning what I was.
好
Okay.
假设这地方
Let's say this place is...
和过去的世界一样
like the old world,
那里有教堂
and they do have a church,
肯定也有妓女吧
then they have to have hookers, too.
对吧  还有赌博
Right? And gambling?
城市的肮脏地带
Shit side of town
瘾君子和亡命徒在那里分享针头
where addicts swap needles with runaways.
这些也都有吧
Got all that, too?
我还没有看到过
I haven't seen any of that.
能把包还给我吗
Can I get my bag back?
我想给你看样东西
I'd like to show you something.
我们就住在那里
That's where we live.
每当人们看到这些照片
Whenever people see those photos,
他们也想住在那里
they want to live there, too.
你就直接让我们进去吗
You'd just let us in?
这么简单吗
That easy?
不  其实一点不简单
No, it's not easy at all, actually.
有一套审查程序
There's a screening process --
试镜啊
An audition.
让我去取踢踏舞鞋
Well, let me get my tap-dancing shoes.
这个
Where is this, uh...
联邦在哪里
Commonwealth located?
他不能告诉你
He can't tell you that.
为什么
Why?
因为你说了算吗
Because you say so?
对  没错
Yeah, that's right.
那我为什么要跟他谈
Then why am I talking to him?
帮我个忙  朋友们
Do me a favor, fellas.
转身看看后面的角落
Turn around and look in that back corner.
他们是抢劫犯  杀人犯
Those are raiders, murderers,
强奸犯  还有几个食人者
rapists, and a few cannibals.
他们都曾坐在你们所坐的座位上
All of them sat in the same seats you're sitting in right now.
大部分都是披着羊皮的狼
Most were wolves dressed as sheep.
他们全都想伤害我的人
All of them meant my people harm.
所以
So...
头狼先生
Mr. Head Wolf...
既然你知道我住哪  我不知道你住哪
if you know where I live and I don't know where you live,
那我放你走该有多蠢啊
how dumb would that be for me to let you go?
你叫什么
What's your name?
托比·卡尔森
Toby Carlson.
托比
Toby...
给老子跪下
get on your goddamn knees!
他妈的坐下
Asses stay in the goddamn chairs!
给老子跪下
Get on your goddamn knees!
-好  -回答问题
- Okay. - Answer the question.
既然你知道我住哪
How dumb would I be to let you go
那我放你走该有多蠢啊
when you know where my home is?
很蠢  好吗
It would be d-dumb, okay?
很蠢
It'd be dumb.
对  很蠢
Yes, it would!
知道吗
You know...
你让我想到了老比利·约翰逊
you remind me of ol' Billy Johnson.
比利几年前来找我们
Billy came to us a few years ago,
许诺在一个遥远的地方
with promises of great wealth and prosperity
有富贵安乐
in a land far away.
但比利没打算带我们去什么乐土
But Billy wasn't gonna bring us to any promised land.
比利只想引诱我们到开阔地
Billy just wanted to get us out in the open
让他的强盗们杀光我们
so his raiders could thoroughly kill us.
比利最后被摆在了架子上
Billy wound up on the shelf
因为他以为我很蠢
because he thought I was stupid.
你也以为我很蠢吗
Do you think I'm stupid, too?
不不不  我不这样想
N-No! No -- no -- no, I do not.
因为比利旁边的架子还空得很呢
Because I've got plenty of room on the shelf right next to Billy!
我不想被摆上架子
I-I don't want to be on the shelf!
我也不认为你蠢  好吗
And I don't think you're stupid! Okay?!
说出你的强盗小队在哪
Tell me where your raiding party is,
不然我将开始杀人
or I'm gonna start dropping bodies on the floor --
-先从他开始  -不
- starting with him! - No!
你觉得我们看起来像强盗吗
Do we look like raiders to you?
披着羊皮的狼  口吐谎言
Wolves dressed as sheep, speaking lies.
你们看起来根本不懂
None of you seem to have any idea
我对这个地方
what my responsibilities are
还有我的人  有多大责任
to this place and to my people.
你们中有没有人想过
Has it occurred to any of you
他们把自己的命托付给了我
that they have entrusted me with their very souls?!
你们为什么来这里
Why did you come here?!
你们想要什么
What you want?!
对呀
Exactly!
你们能有什么我们想要的东西
What do you have that we would want?
这地方是个粪坑  我们能要什么
This place is a shithole! Why would we want it?!
肉
The meat.
你们要肉
You want the meat.
你以为我们是食人者吗
You think we're cannibals?
带着包装好的即食口粮来的食人者吗
Cannibals who came in with prepackaged MREs?
这就是你的逻辑吗
That's what you're going with?
我们只是给了你们食物和水
All we've done is given you food and water.
你们现在没挨饿全是因为我们
You aren't starving right now because of us!
这是真相  还是谎言
Is that real? Or is that a lie?
你知道还有什么是真的吗
You know what else is real?
照片里的那些士兵
The soldiers in those photos.
如果我们不回去
If we don't get back,
他们会来这里  杀了你们所有人
they'll come in here and kill all of you.
或者谁都不用死  好吗
Or nobody dies, okay?
你放我们走  可以救你自己和你的人
You save yourself and your people by letting us go,
我们将永远不再回来
and we will never come back here again.
我们将永远不再烦你
We will never bother you.
我保证  好吗
I promise that, okay?
多糟糕的一天
What a day.
真是该死的一天
What a goddamn day.
你们离开这里
You will leave here.
永远不准回来
You will never come back.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我的工作
My job.
他准备放我们走的
He was gonna let us go!
闭嘴
Shut up!
把他当做人质
Keep him hostage.
锁上门
And lock this door.
安全以后我会回来
I'll be back when it's safe.
一周又一小时前
进
Yeah?
哥们
Hey, bud.
我收到你的讯息了
I got your... call.
怎么了
What's up?
不了  下个月就戒酒满四年了
Ah, no -- four years sober next month.
出什么事了
What is wrong?
我知道我说服弥尔顿同意的
You know how I got Milton to agree to this whole
弗吉尼亚州的几个乡下村镇的援建项目吧
communal project with these hick towns out in Virginia?
知道
Yeah.
她给了我很多资源
So she's released a lot of resources for me.
我利用其中一些资源  为另一件事派出了
And I used some of them to send out a convoy full of supplies.
一支装满物资的车队
For that other thing.
车队上周没有报到
Convoy didn't check in last week,
所以我派侦察队去查看情况
so I sent out scouts to see what happened.
车队被劫了
It was hijacked.
护卫的士兵全死了
Troopers guarding it, all dead.
天啊
Oh, God.
谁干的
Who was it?
踪迹指向了一座公寓楼  某个团体盘踞在那里
Tracks led to an apartment complex where some group is holed up.
首领穿得像个将军
Leader dresses like a general.
又是个军阀
Another warlord.
追随者还信教
Followers are religious, too.
周二和周日会做弥撒
Mass on Tuesdays and Sundays.
真可爱
Cute.
他们现在拿到了你的枪
And they've got your guns now.
我估计还有货物吧
And the cargo, too, I take it?
好吧  我错过了什么
Okay. What am I missing?
不过是个军阀  灭了就行
It's just some warlord. Snuff them out.
要做最坏的打算
Assume the worst
顶楼上有枪指着所有方向
that the guns are pointing out of those top floors in all directions.
如果我派小队去  还没到门口就被干掉了
I send in a squad, they get cut down before they hit the door.
那就别派小队去  派一个连的人去
Then don't send a squad, send a company.
然后夷平整座楼
Then raze the whole building.
我要一百个士兵  弥尔顿肯定会注意到
I ask for a hundred troops, there's no way Milton doesn't notice.
"怎么回事  兰斯
"What happened, Lance?
看起来不太对啊  兰斯"
This seems like quite the misfire, Lance."
不  我要手术刀式的行动
No, I need a surgical solution.
天啊
Oh, man.
我不再做那种事了  兰斯
I don't do that anymore, Lance.
得了吧
Come on.
我需要那个过去在这里
I need the former CIA guy
铲除反叛者的前中情局特工
who helped root out disobedient shits from here back in the day.
我需要一个刺客
I need an assassin.
听着
Listen,
我喜欢退休生活
I like being retired.
我醒来  冥想
I get up, I meditate,
然后出门 寻找需要帮助的人
then I get to go out and find people who need help
给他们第二次机会
and give 'em a second chance.
这很禅意  感觉很棒
It's Zen. It feels great.
这种生活也能被夺走
And it can be taken from you.
你啊
You, um...
活得不耐烦了吗  兰斯
You tired of living, Lance?
大部分死去的士兵都是二十来岁的孩子
Most of the dead troopers are kids in their 20s.
这是我造成的
That's on me.
我必须做出弥补
I need to make it right.
好吧
Okay.
你的计划是什么
What are you thinking?
-亚伦干得还好吗  -很好
- How's Aaron working out? - He's great.
他能立即与人相处融洽
He instantly connects with people.
-让我的工作更轻松  -很好
- Makes my job easy. - Great.
你知道他的那个神父朋友吗
Do you know about his buddy, the priest?
好嘛
Stokes.
我懂了
Okay, okay.
所以我们去接触他们
So we go in like we're making first contact,
因为他们信教
and then, since they are religious...
神父能让他们放松警惕  他们会让你们进去
Priest gets their guard down, they let you in,
去见那个老大  然后
go see the big chief, and then...
做你擅长的事
do what you do.
万一动手以后
And what about when things turn
我必须告诉他们真相呢
and I have to tell them what's what?
他们会听话的
They'll fall in line.
每个人都是如此
Everyone does.
去查后面
Sweep the rear.
你劫的枪和货物
The guns and the cargo you hijacked.
你靠屠杀我的士兵得到的东西  在哪里
The ones that you massacred my soldiers to get to, where are they?
我不知道你在说什么
I got no idea what you're talking about.
从那里到这里有三组踪迹
Three sets of tracks led back here from there.
你要不再说一次
You wanna try again?
那个车队啊
That caravan.
我们发现时就已经是那样了
Yeah, we -- we found it like that.
你刚骗了我
You just lied to me.
住手  住手
Stop! Stop.
铐住他
Cuff him!
没种的家伙
Hey, dickless.
如果是我找到了那批武器  你不觉得我
If I found those weapons, don't you think I --
准备好架子  军阀
Ready the shelf, warlord.
最上层  正中央
Top shelf, dead center.
听起来怎样
How's that sound?
就在比利上面
Right above Billy.
你怎么啦
Hey! Hey, where'd you go, huh?
大话那么多  却死这么快
All that talk, and you died so quick.
别用那种表情看我
Don't you look at me like that.
他是个该死的畜生
He's a damn animal.
我们的工作应该是帮助别人
We are supposed to be helping people.
没错
We are.
这是工作的另一面
This is the other side of it.
消除威胁
Snuffing out threats.
这样才能让世界更安全
This is how we make the world safe.
看住他
Hold him.
干掉他
Pop him!
有意思
Interesting.
-来啊  -来吧
- Come on. - Let's go.
我们要追吗
Do we follow?
长官
Sir!
我就他妈的转身了一会儿
I turn my back for one goddamn minute!
把我的盔甲拿来
Get me my armor.
他是只狼  正如他们的首领所说
He was a wolf, just like their leader said.
你认为货物被盗也是他在撒谎吗
Think he was lying about the stolen shipments?
我不知道
I don't know.
联邦要那么多枪做什么
What would the Commonwealth want with all those guns?
这是进去的最佳路线吗
This the best way in?
是的  但是
Yeah, but...
这是你从哪里拿到的
where'd you get that?
你给了那个骑马来山顶寨的人
You gave it to the guy who rode into Hilltop.
我没有
No, I didn't.
那是谁给的
Then who did?
12个小时前
袭击发生时
别紧张  姑娘
Easy, girl.
不许动
Don't move.
你们有多少人
How many of you are there?
12个人
12.
他们有什么武器
What are they armed with?
机枪
Machine guns.
我不知情
I didn't know.
情况怎样
What's it look like?
死了很多人
A lot dead.
为首的人在和另外两个人吵架
Guy in charge is arguing with two others --
一个神父  还有一个手臂是流星锤的人
a priest and a guy with a spiked ball for an arm.
该死
Shit.
加百利和亚伦
Gabriel and Aaron.
你认识他们吗
You know them?
他们也不知情
They didn't know, either.
我们来自一个叫联邦的地方
We come from a place called The Commonwealth.
-这不是我想做的事  -闭嘴
- This isn't what I signed up for. - Shut up.
在这里有个社区
There's a community right here.
你去找玛姬  别找别人
You ask for Maggie, no one else.
告诉她  加百利和亚伦有麻烦了
You tell her Gabriel and Aaron are in trouble.
走  快走
Go. Go!
这是工作的另一面
This is the other side of it.
消除威胁
Snuffing out threats.
这样才能让世界更安全
This is how we make the world safe.
尼根
Negan?
加百利
Gabe.
-有意思  -来了两个人  我们得走了
- Interesting. - Two coming in. We gotta go!
-我们得走了  -我们不能丢下他
- We gotta go! - We can't leave him.
如果你出去  我们都会死
If you go out there, we all die.
走吧
Come on.
长官
Sir!
我就他妈的转身了一会儿
I turn my back for one goddamn minute!
现在
大楼的居民们
Residents of The Complex.
你们已被视为联邦的敌人
You have been deemed enemies of The Commonwealth.
你们中的某人偷了我们的东西
One of you has stolen from us.
这可不行
That cannot stand.
坏消息是  你们的军阀死了
Bad news is, your warlord is dead.
好消息是  你们仍能改邪归正
The good news is, you still can make things right.
把东西还给我们  我们就离开
Gives us what's ours, and we'll leave.
到此为止
That'll be that.
-武器在哪  -我不知道
- Where are the weapons? - I don't know.
快问他们
Then ask them -- quickly.
加百利  她说他们没有就是没有
Gabe, if she says they don't have them, they don't have them.
你不明白
You don't understand.
我在祈祷你们真的偷了那些东西
I'm praying that you did steal them
因为没那些东西  我们就死定了
because without them, we're dead.
他不会放我们任何人活着离开的
He's not gonna let any of us leave here alive.
我的武器在哪
Where are my weapons?
我不知道
I don't know.
你是真不知道  对吧
You really don't, do you?
对
No.
好吧
Okay.
我信你
I believe you.
你呢
And how about you?
你们的人让你们失望了
Your people have let you down!
搜查每个房间
Hit each room.
不开口的人全杀了
Kill anyone who won't talk.
收到
Copy that.
我们现在要团结一致
What we need to do now is stick together.
别想着投降或乞求原谅了
You can forget about giving up or begging for forgiveness.
伊恩已经死了
Ian's dead.
但他不是我们的第一位首领
But he wasn't our first leader.
我们不是靠他才生存这么久的
He wasn't what kept us together this long.
我们靠的是自己  靠的是像家人一样团结协作
We did, and we did it by working together as a family.
现在  我们的家人们
And right now, our family's scattered
散落在这栋楼里  但你们知道吗
all over this building, but you know what?
我们比闯进我们家的混蛋们更了解这里
We know this place better than the assholes in our house do.
我们会取得最后的胜利
We're coming out of this on top.
真是...
So that was, um...
说得挺好的
That's pretty good.
他们干掉了我们最好的人
They -- They took out our best.
对  但他们需要听到这些话
Yeah, but they needed to hear it.
霍奇斯  回话  东侧安全吗
Hodges, come in. Is the east end clear?
霍奇斯  收到了吗
Hodges, do you copy?
东侧...
Is the east end --